toshiba.ca 2019-04-06

# Toshiba of Canada Limited

TOSHIBA OF CANADA LIMITED PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT

This Privacy Policy Statement (“Privacy Statement”) applies solely to the online information gathering and data sharing practices of Toshiba of Canada Limited (as follows, "Toshiba ", "we", "us" or “our”) for this Web Site, service and/or application (“Toshiba Online”) and does not apply to other Toshiba affiliates or our parent company, and such entities may have their own privacy policies.

We are proud to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, by complying with the laws and regulations under applicable privacy laws in Canada, including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act.

From time to time, we may make changes to this Privacy Statement. The Privacy Statement is current as of the "last revised" date which appears at the top of this page. We will treat Personal Information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Statement under which it was collected and our Privacy Policy, unless we have your consent to treat it differently. This Privacy Statement applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source.

By using Toshiba Online, you agree to the terms provided in this Privacy Statement, which are as follows:

1. To which companies does this Privacy Statement apply?

This Privacy Statement applies to the collections, uses and disclosures of Personal Information by Toshiba of Canada Limited. 

2. What is Personal Information? 

“Personal Information” is information about an identifiable individual. This information may include but is not limited to your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, domain name, client IP address, facsimile number, credit card number, household income, banking information, creditor information, and other personally identifiable information about you. 

3. How do we collect your Personal Information? 

We may collect Personal Information and the products or services you purchase or obtain from us. This information is collected, in general, from information you provide to us through Toshiba Online when you complete a product registration or initial setup, through your survey responses or rebate forms, and/or through your filling out and submitting forms through Toshiba Online requesting information from Toshiba, as well as when you register your product for warranties and/or speak to a Toshiba representative.  We may also collect Personal Information in other circumstances when we have obtained your consent to do so or as otherwise permitted or required by law. With your consent, we may also collect your precise geographic location information via Toshiba Online.

4. What about "cookies"? 

Toshiba may collect information during your website visit through use of a "cookie" to track how our visitors use this site and understand trends and patterns. These cookies provide anonymous traffic insights that are used to assess site efficiency and allow us to enhance your future online experiences with Toshiba. 

We may engage third parties to collect non-personal information using "cookies" and/or other industry standard technologies (e.g., clear GIFS, web beacons, pixel tags, javascript tag) to generate statistics or measure and analyze website activity (including page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites and/or the items you view or place in your shopping bag) in order to improve Toshiba Online functionality, deliver content specific to you and/or targeted for your interests while using Toshiba Online and/or a third party web site, and to better manage advertising of our products. The collected data also helps us determine which product, service or support information may be appropriate for you and to help us maintain an efficient shopping experience for you.

You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a "cookie" or to turn off "cookies" completely. If you do so, however, some areas of our site may not function properly

5. Where do we use and store your Personal Information? 

We will keep the Personal Information that we collect primarily at our offices or on our servers (or those of our affiliates or service providers).  While our affiliates and service providers may, from time to time, also hold your Personal Information in connection with purposes for which you provided your consent or as otherwise permitted or required by law, we remain responsible, and remain the contacts for, such information. 

We generally identify the purposes for which we use your Personal Information at the time we collect such information from you. We generally use your Personal Information for the following purposes (the “Purposes”): (i) to provide the products, services or information you have requested; (ii) to complete your service requests; (iii) to assist you with technical support; (iv) to gather your opinion and feedback through surveys; (v) to enrol you in our contests or promotional programs; (vi) to include you on our mailing list; and (vii) to process your application for employment.  We may use your Personal Information for other purposes with your consent or as permitted or required by law.

6. To whom do we provide your Personal Information? 

We may disclose your Personal Information to third party service providers with whom we have contractual agreements that include appropriate privacy standards, where such third parties are assisting us with certain services (i.e. third parties may be used for registration of a training event). We may also disclose Personal Information to a potential or actual acquirer in connection with a transaction involving the sale of the business of Toshiba or its assets or as otherwise permitted or required by law. In addition, we may send Personal Information outside of Canada, including to the United States, for the purposes set out above, including for process and storage by service providers in connection with such purposes, and you should note that while such information is out of the country, it is subject to the laws of the country in which it is held, and may be subject to disclosure to the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of such other country, pursuant to the laws of such country. 

We do not sell your Personal Information. We may use your personal information to contact you about products you have purchased, inform you of product and service opportunities that may be of interest to you, to conduct market research regarding Toshiba products or services, to customize the content of Toshiba Online for you, to support and enhance our communications with you, or for other business purposes. We may share your personal information within the Toshiba family of companies for business purposes and with other companies who provide marketing or other services on our behalf and at our direction, but we do not permit them to use such personal information that we have shared for their own direct marketing purposes. We may share your personal information outside of the Toshiba family with companies in connection with your trial, purchase or registration of products or services provided by such companies and with companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf and at our direction. We may also share your personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, and other legal action, or if Toshiba reasonably believes it is appropriate to do so to protect Toshiba, its customers or the public.

7. When and how do we obtain your consent? 

We obtain your consent prior to collecting, using or disclosing your Personal Information, except where collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information without consent is permitted or required by law. Consent for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information may be express or implied, or may be obtained through opt-out methods.  You may provide your consent to us either orally, electronically or in writing.  You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information at any time subject to contractual and legal restrictions.  However, if you withdraw your consent to certain collections, uses or disclosures of your Personal Information, we may no longer be able to provide certain products or services.   

8. Third Party Web Sites

Toshiba Online may contain links to other third party web sites that are not operated by us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party web sites. The information practices of those third party web sites are not covered by this Privacy Statement. Other Toshiba co-branded web sites may also operate under their own privacy and security policies. You are responsible for reviewing third party and co-branded privacy policies, as applicable, to determine the handling of your information.

9. How do we ensure the privacy of your Personal Information when dealing with our affiliates and other third parties?

We take reasonable steps to ensure that all affiliates and other third parties that are retained to perform services on our behalf and are provided with Personal Information are contractually required to observe the intent of this Privacy Statement and our Privacy Policy and practices.   

10. How long will we utilize, disclose or retain your Personal Information? 

We may keep a record of your Personal Information, correspondence or comments in a file specific to you. We will utilize, disclose or retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which that Personal Information was collected and as permitted or required by law.  

11. How can you review your Personal Information that we have collected, utilized or disclosed? 

If you make a written request to review any Personal Information about you that we have collected, utilized or disclosed, we will provide you with any such Personal Information to the extent required by law. We will make such Personal Information available to you in a form that is generally understandable, and will explain any abbreviations or codes.  

12. How do you know that the Personal Information we have on you is accurate?

We will ensure that your Personal Information is kept as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary for the purposes for which we intend to use it. We will not routinely update your Personal Information, unless such a process is necessary. We expect you, from time to time, to supply us with written updates to your Personal Information, when required. 

13. What if the Personal Information we have on you is inaccurate? 

At any time, you can challenge the accuracy or completeness of your Personal Information in our records. If you successfully demonstrate that your Personal Information in our records is inaccurate or incomplete, we will amend the Personal Information as required. Where appropriate, we will transmit the amended information to third parties having access to your Personal Information. 

14. How fast will we respond to your written requests? 

We will attempt to respond to each of your written requests not later than thirty (30) days after receipt of such requests. We will advise you in writing if we cannot meet your requests within this time limit. You have the right to make a complaint to the federal Privacy Commissioner in respect of this time limit. 

15. Are there any costs to you for requesting information about your Personal Information or our Privacy Policy or practices? 

We will not charge any costs for you to access your Personal Information in our records or to access our Privacy Policy or practices without first providing you with an estimate of the approximate costs, if any. You may withdraw your requests for access to information by notifying us within the thirty (30) day notice period disclosed on the estimate. If you do not notify us within such thirty (30) day period, we will send you a further notice indicating that you will be deemed to have withdrawn your request for access unless you advise us otherwise within thirty (30) days. If, after the expiry of this second thirty (30) day period, you have not so advised us, we will deem your request to have been withdrawn and provide you with written notice to that effect.  

16. How do we know that it is really you requesting your Personal Information? 

We may request that you provide sufficient identification to permit us to verify your identity before granting access to, or confirming the existence, use or disclosure of your Personal Information. Any such identifying information shall be used only for this purpose. 

17. What safeguards have we implemented to protect your Personal Information? 

We have implemented physical, organizational, contractual and technological security measures to protect your Personal Information from loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. However, you should understand that absolute security cannot be guaranteed and we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.  The only employees who are granted access to your Personal Information are those with a business ‘need-to-know’ or whose duties reasonably require such information.  

18. Notifications of Changes

From time to time, we may choose to change our privacy practices and this Privacy Statement. We will notify you of material changes to the Privacy Statement by posting a revised Privacy Statement via Toshiba Online with an updated effective date. We recommend that you check back at Toshiba Online at www.toshiba.ca/Privacy_Policy/ on a periodic basis to review the then current Privacy Statement. Any updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments to this Privacy Statement shall be effective immediately upon its posting via Toshiba Online and will only be applicable to disputes arising, or arising out of events occurring, after such posting has been made. You agree that you will continue to be bound by this Privacy Statement, however and whenever it is updated, revised, supplemented, modified, or amended, if you continue to use Toshiba Online after, the updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments have been posted.  This Privacy Statement is effective as of May 1, 2017.

19. How do you contact us regarding access to your Personal Information or our Privacy Policy and practices?

All requests for access to or correction of your Personal Information, as well as any comments, questions, concerns or complaints regarding your Personal Information or our Privacy Policy and practices, should be forwarded to our Privacy Officer as follows:  

In writing: 

Privacy Officer 

Toshiba of Canada Limited 

75 Tiverton Court

Markham, ON L3R 4M8 

Email: privacyofficer@toshiba.ca 

Copyright© 2017Toshiba of Canada Limited. All rights reserved
